A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1947-1951 FA759
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1949
  - France - Medical Sciences, 1949; 02.1949/500.A
    - France, 1949 (Box 463, Folder 3103)
  - France - Nursing, 1949; 02.1949/500.C
    - France, 1949 (Box 463, Folder 3103)
  - France - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1949; 02.1949/500.E
    - France, 1949 (Box 463, Folder 3103)
  - France - Public Health Education, 1949; 02.1949/500.L
    - France, 1949 (Box 463, Folder 3103)
  - France - Humanities and Arts, 1949; 02.1949/500.R
    - France, 1949 (Box 463, Folder 3104)
  - Asia, 1949; 02.1949/600
    - Asia, 1949 (Box 463, Folder 3105)
  - Asia - Humanities and Arts, 1949; 02.1949/600.R
    - Asia, 1949 (Box 463, Folder 3105)
  - China, 1949; 02.1949/601
    - China - Administration, 1949 (Box 463, Folder 3106)
    - China - Administration, 1949 (Box 463, Folder 3107)
    - China - (A-Z), 1949 (Box 463, Folder 3108)
    - China - (A-Z), 1949 (Box 463, Folder 3109)
  - China - Nursing, 1949; 02.1949/601.C
    - China, 1949 (Box 464, Folder 3110)
  - China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1949; 02.1949/601.E
    - China, 1949 (Box 464, Folder 3110)
  - China - Public Health Education, 1949; 02.1949/601.L
    - China, 1949 (Box 464, Folder 3110)
  - China - Humanities and Arts, 1949; 02.1949/601.R
    - China, 1949 (Box 464, Folder 3110)
  - Taiwan, 1949; 02.1949/605
    - Taiwan, 1949 (Box 464, Folder 3110)
  - Taiwan - Medical Sciences, 1949; 02.1949/605.A
    - Taiwan, 1949 (Box 464, Folder 3110)
  - Taiwan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Award, 1949; 02.1949/605.E
    - Taiwan, 1949 (Box 464, Folder 3110)
  - Japan, 1949; 02.1949/609
    - Japan - (A-Z), 1949 (Box 464, Folder 3111)
    - Japan - (A-Z), 1949 (Box 464, Folder 3112)
    - Japan - Population, 1949 (Box 464, Folder 3113)
  - Japan - Medical Sciences, 1949; 02.1949/609.A
    - Japan, 1949 (Box 464, Folder 3114)
  - Japan - Nursing, 1949; 02.1949/609.C
    - Japan, 1949 (Box 464, Folder 3114)
  - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1949; 02.1949/609.E
    - Japan, 1949 (Box 464, Folder 3114)
  - Korea, 1949; 02.1949/613
    - Korea, 1949 (Box 464, Folder 3114)
  - Korea - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1949; 02.1949/613.E
    - Korea, 1949 (Box 464, Folder 3114)
  - Korea - Humanities and Arts, 1949; 02.1949/613.R
    - Korea, 1949 (Box 464, Folder 3114)
  - Thailand, 1949; 02.1949/617
    - Thailand, 1949 (Box 464, Folder 3114)
  - Thailand - Medical Sciences, 1949; 02.1949/617.A
    - Thailand, 1949 (Box 464, Folder 3114)
  - Thailand - Humanities and Arts, 1949; 02.1949/617.R
    - Thailand, 1949 (Box 464, Folder 3114)
  - Southeast Asia, 1949; 02.1949/625
    - Southeast Asia, 1949 (Box 464, Folder 3115)
  - Holland, 1949; 02.1949/650
    - Netherlands - (A-S), 1949 (Box 464, Folder 3115)
    - Netherlands - (S-Z), 1949 (Box 465, Folder 3116)
  - Holland - Medical Sciences, 1949; 02.1949/650.A
    - Netherlands, 1949 (Box 465, Folder 3116)
  - Holland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1949; 02.1949/650.E
    - Netherlands, 1949 (Box 465, Folder 3116)
  - Holland - Humanities and Arts, 1949; 02.1949/650.R
    - Netherlands, 1949 (Box 465, Folder 3116)
  - Indonesia, 1949; 02.1949/652
    - Indonesia, 1949 (Box 465, Folder 3117)
  - Indonesia - Humanities and Arts, 1949; 02.1949/652.R
    - Indonesia, 1949 (Box 465, Folder 3117)
  - Java, 1949; 02.1949/655
    - Java, 1949 (Box 465, Folder 3117)
  - Europe, 1949; 02.1949/700
    - Europe, 1949 (Box 465, Folder 3118)
  - Afghanistan, 1949; 02.1949/703
    - Afghanistan, 1949 (Box 465, Folder 3119)
  - Austria, 1949; 02.1949/705
    - Austria, 1949 (Box 465, Folder 3119)
  - Austria - Medical Sciences, 1949; 02.1949/705.A
    - Austria, 1949 (Box 465, Folder 3119)
  - Austria - Humanities and Arts, 1949; 02.1949/705.R
    - Austria, 1949 (Box 465, Folder 3119)
  - Belgium, 1949; 02.1949/707
    - Belgium, 1949 (Box 465, Folder 3120)
  - Belgium - Medical Sciences, 1949; 02.1949/707.A
    - Belgium, 1949 (Box 465, Folder 3120)
  - Belgium - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1949; 02.1949/707.E
    - Belgium, 1949 (Box 465, Folder 3120)
  - Zaire, 1949; 02.1949/709
    - Zaire, 1949 (Box 465, Folder 3120)
  - Yugoslavia, 1949; 02.1949/710
    - Yugoslavia, 1949 (Box 465, Folder 3120)
  - Bulgaria, 1949; 02.1949/711
    - Bulgaria, 1949 (Box 465, Folder 3120)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1949; 02.1949/712
    - Czechoslovakia, 1949 (Box 465, Folder 3120)
  - Czechoslovakia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1949; 02.1949/712.E
    - Czechoslovakia, 1949 (Box 465, Folder 3120)
  - Denmark, 1949; 02.1949/713
    - Denmark, 1949 (Box 465, Folder 3121)
  - Denmark - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1949; 02.1949/713.D
    - Denmark, 1949 (Box 465, Folder 3121)
  - Denmark - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1949; 02.1949/713.E
    - Denmark, 1949 (Box 465, Folder 3122)
  - Denmark - Humanities and Arts, 1949; 02.1949/713.R
    - Denmark, 1949 (Box 465, Folder 3122)
  - Iceland, 1949; 02.1949/715
    - Iceland, 1949 (Box 465, Folder 3122)
  - Germany, 1949; 02.1949/717
    - Germany - (A-U), 1949 (Box 466, Folder 3123)
    - Germany - (A-U), 1949 (Box 466, Folder 3124)
    - Germany - (A-U), 1949 (Box 466, Folder 3125)
    - Germany - (A-U), 1949 (Box 466, Folder 3126)
  - Germany - Medical Sciences, 1949; 02.1949/717.A
    - Germany, 1949 (Box 466, Folder 3126)
  - Germany - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1949; 02.1949/717.D
    - Germany, 1949 (Box 466, Folder 3127)
  - Germany - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1949; 02.1949/717.E
    - Germany, 1949 (Box 466, Folder 3127)
  - Germany - Humanities and Arts, 1949; 02.1949/717.R
    - Germany, 1949 (Box 466, Folder 3127)
  - Germany - Social Sciences, 1949; 02.1949/717.S
    - Germany, 1949 (Box 466, Folder 3127)
  - Angaur Island, 1949; 02.1949/741
    - Angaur Island, 1949 (Box 466, Folder 3128)
  - Greece, 1949; 02.1949/749
    - Greece, 1949 (Box 466, Folder 3128)
  - Hungary, 1949; 02.1949/750
    - Hungary, 1949 (Box 466, Folder 3128)
  - Hungary - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1949; 02.1949/750.E
    - Hungary, 1949 (Box 466, Folder 3128)
  - Italy, 1949; 02.1949/751
    - Italy, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3129)
  - Italy - Medical Sciences, 1949; 02.1949/751.A
    - Italy, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3130)
  - Italy - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1949; 02.1949/751.E
    - Italy, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3130)
  - Italy - Humanities and Arts, 1949; 02.1949/751.R
    - Italy, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3130)
  - Norway, 1949; 02.1949/767
    - Norway, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3130)
  - Norway - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1949; 02.1949/767.E
    - Norway, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3130)
  - Norway - Humanities and Arts, 1949; 02.1949/767.R
    - Norway, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3130)
  - Iran, 1949; 02.1949/771
    - Iran, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3131)
  - Iran - Medical Sciences, 1949; 02.1949/771.A
    - Iran, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3131)
  - Iran - Nursing, 1949; 02.1949/771.C
    - Iran, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3132)
  - Iran - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1949; 02.1949/771.E
    - Iran, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3133)
  - Iran - Malaria, 1949; 02.1949/771.I
    - Iran, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3133)
  - Portugal, 1949; 02.1949/773
    - Portugal, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3134)
  - Portugal - Medical Sciences, 1949; 02.1949/773.A
    - Portugal, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3134)
  - Portugal - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1949; 02.1949/773.E
    - Portugal, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3134)
  - Portugal - Malaria, 1949; 02.1949/773.I
    - Portugal, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3134)
  - Ukraine, 1949; 02.1949/784
    - Ukraine, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3134)
  - USSR, 1949; 02.1949/785
    - USSR, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3134)
    - USSR, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3134)
  - USSR - Humanities and Arts, 1949; 02.1949/785.R
    - USSR, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3134)
  - Latvia, 1949; 02.1949/786
    - Latvia, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3134)
  - Finland, 1949; 02.1949/787
    - Finland, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3134)
  - Finland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1949; 02.1949/787.E
    - Finland, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3134)
  - Finland - Public Health Demonstrations, 1949; 02.1949/787.J
    - Finland, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3134)
  - Poland, 1949; 02.1949/789
    - Poland, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3135)
  - Poland - Medical Sciences, 1949; 02.1949/789.A
    - Poland, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3135)
  - Poland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1949; 02.1949/789.E
    - Poland, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3135)
  - Spain, 1949; 02.1949/795
    - Spain, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3135)
  - Spain - Medical Sciences, 1949; 02.1949/795.A
    - Spain, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3135)
  - Spain - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1949; 02.1949/795.E
    - Spain, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3135)
  - Spain - Malaria, 1949; 02.1949/795.I
    - Spain, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3135)
  - Sweden, 1949; 02.1949/800
    - Sweden, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3136)
  - Sweden - Medical Sciences, 1949; 02.1949/800.A
    - Sweden, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3136)
  - Liechtenstein, 1949; 02.1949/802
  - Liechtenstein - Malaria, 1949; 02.1949/802.I
    - Liechtenstein, 1949 (Box 467, Folder 3136)
  - Switzerland, 1949; 02.1949/803
    - Switzerland, 1949 (Box 468, Folder 3137)
  - Switzerland - Medical Sciences, 1949; 02.1949/803.A
    - Switzerland, 1949 (Box 468, Folder 3137)
  - Switzerland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1949; 02.1949/803.E
    - Switzerland, 1949 (Box 468, Folder 3137)
  - Near East Region, 1949; 02.1949/804
    - Near East, 1949 (Box 468, Folder 3138)
  - Near East Region - Humanities and Arts, 1949; 02.1949/804.R
    - Near East, 1949 (Box 468, Folder 3138)
  - Turkey, 1949; 02.1949/805
    - Turkey, 1949 (Box 468, Folder 3138)
  - Turkey - Nursing, 1949; 02.1949/805.C
    - Turkey, 1949 (Box 468, Folder 3138)
  - Turkey - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1949; 02.1949/805.E
    - Turkey, 1949 (Box 468, Folder 3138)
  - Turkey - Humanities and Arts, 1949; 02.1949/805.R
    - Turkey, 1949 (Box 468, Folder 3138)
  - Cyprus, 1949; 02.1949/809
    - Cyprus, 1949 (Box 468, Folder 3139)
  - Israel, 1949; 02.1949/825
    - Israel, 1949 (Box 468, Folder 3139)
  - Israel - Medical Sciences, 1949; 02.1949/825.A
    - Israel, 1949 (Box 468, Folder 3139)
  - Lebanon, 1949; 02.1949/833
    - Lebanon, 1949 (Box 468, Folder 3139)
  - Lebanon - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1949; 02.1949/833.E
    - Lebanon, 1949 (Box 468, Folder 3139)
- General Correspondence, 1950
  - International, 1950; 02.1950/100
    - Staff - International - Aitken, Thomas H. G., 1950 (Box 468, Folder 3140)
    - Staff - International - Anderson, Richmond K., 1950 (Box 468, Folder 3141)
    - Staff - International - Balfour, Marshall C., 1950 (Box 468, Folder 3142)
    - Staff - International - Barnard, Chester I., 1950 (Box 468, Folder 3143)
    - Staff - International - Bates, Marston, 1950 (Box 469, Folder 3144)
    - Staff - International - Belknap, Chauncey - Bevier, George, 1950 (Box 469, Folder 3145)
    - Staff - International - Buchanan, Norman S. - Bugher, John C. - Burden, Robert P., 1950 (Box 469, Folder 3146)
    - Staff - International - Carr, Henry P., 1950 (Box 469, Folder 3147)
    - Staff - International - Carter, Joseph C., 1950 (Box 469, Folder 3148)
    - Staff - International - Causey, Ottis R., 1950 (Box 469, Folder 3149)
    - Staff - International - D'Arms, Edward F. - Diplomatic Service, 1950 (Box 469, Folder 3150)
    - Staff - International - Dyer, Brian R. - Elmendorf, John E., 1950 (Box 470, Folder 3151)
    - Staff - International - Evans, Roger F. - Fahs, Charles Burton, 1950 (Box 470, Folder 3152)
    - Staff - International - Gilpatric, Chadboune, 1950 (Box 470, Folder 3153)
    - Staff - International - Grant, John B., 1950 (Box 470, Folder 3154)
    - Staff - International - Gregg, Alan - Hahn, Richard G., 1950 (Box 470, Folder 3155)
    - Staff - International - Hayes, Guy S., 1950 (Box 470, Folder 3156)
    - Staff - International - Hill, Rolla B. - Hirst, Esther Mary - Hughes, Thomas P., 1950 (Box 470, Folder 3157)
    - Staff - International - Institute - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 471, Folder 3158)
    - Staff - International - International - (A-D), 1950 (Box 471, Folder 3159)
    - Staff - International - Educational - Exchange, 1950 (Box 471, Folder 3160)
    - Staff - International - (F-Z), 1950 (Box 471, Folder 3161)
    - Staff - International - Janney, John H., 1950 (Box 471, Folder 3162)
    - Staff - International - Johnson, Harold N. - Kendrick, John F. - Kerr, J. Austin, 1950 (Box 471, Folder 3163)
    - Staff - International - Kimball, Lindsley F. - Kitchen, Stuart F., 1950 (Box 471, Folder 3164)
    - Staff - International - Logan, John A. - 1, 1950 (Box 471, Folder 3165)
    - Staff - International - Logan, John A. - 2, 1950 (Box 472, Folder 3166)
    - Staff - International - Loomis, William F. - McCoy, Oliver R., 1950 (Box 472, Folder 3167)
    - Staff - International - McIntosh, W. A., 1950 (Box 472, Folder 3168)
    - Staff - International - McIntosh, W. A., 1950 (Box 472, Folder 3169)
    - Staff - International - Magoon, Estus H. - Maier, John, 1950 (Box 472, Folder 3170)
    - Staff - International - Marshall, John - Miller, Harry M., 1950 (Box 472, Folder 3171)
    - Staff - International - Morison, Robert S. - Noll, Anna Mary, 1950 (Box 473, Folder 3172)
    - Staff - International - Pan American Institute of Geography and History - Paul, J. Harland - Payne, George C., 1950 (Box 473, Folder 3173)
    - Staff - International - Peterson, Osler J., 1950 (Box 473, Folder 3174)
    - Staff - International - Pomerat, Gerard R. - Rhind, Flora M. - Rickard, E. R., 1950 (Box 473, Folder 3175)
    - Staff - International - Russell, Paul F., 1950 (Box 473, Folder 3176)
    - Staff - International - Ryan, Bryce - Sasse, Bruce E. - Smith, Hugh H. - Smithburn, Kenneth C., 1950 (Box 473, Folder 3177)
    - Staff - International - Strode, George K. - Taylor, Richard M., 1950 (Box 473, Folder 3178)
    - Staff - International - Tennant, Mary Elizabeth, 1950 (Box 474, Folder 3179)
    - Staff - International - United Nations - (A-D), 1950 (Box 474, Folder 3180)
    - Staff - International - UNESCO, 1950 (Box 474, Folder 3181)
    - Staff - International - UNESCO - (A-N), 1950 (Box 474, Folder 3182)
    - Staff - International - UNESCO - (A-N), 1950 (Box 474, Folder 3183)
    - Staff - International - UNESCO - (A-N), 1950 (Box 474, Folder 3184)
    - Staff - International - UNESCO - (P-Z), 1950 (Box 475, Folder 3185)
    - Staff - International - United Nations - (F-Z), 1950 (Box 475, Folder 3186)
    - Staff - International - United Nations - (F-Z), 1950 (Box 475, Folder 3187)
    - Staff - International - United Nations - W. H. O., 1950 (Box 475, Folder 3188)
    - Staff - International - Varley, Margaret L. - Warren, Andrew J., 1950 (Box 475, Folder 3189)
    - Staff - International - Watson, Robert B., 1950 (Box 475, Folder 3190)
    - Staff - International - Watson, Robert B., 1950 (Box 475, Folder 3191)
    - Staff - International - Weaver, Warren - Webb, Vanderbilt, 1950 (Box 476, Folder 3192)
    - Staff - International - Weir, John M. - 1, 1950 (Box 476, Folder 3193)
    - Staff - International - Weir, John M. - 2 - Wells, Clifford W., 1950 (Box 476, Folder 3194)
    - Staff - International - Whitman, Loring - Willits, Joseph H., 1950 (Box 476, Folder 3195)
    - Staff - International - Wilson, D. Bruce - Wright, Daniel E., 1950 (Box 476, Folder 3196)
    - Staff - International - Worth, C. Brooke, 1950 (Box 476, Folder 3197)
    - Staff - International - Worth, C. Brooke, 1950 (Box 476, Folder 3198)
    - Staff - International - Miscellany - (A-G), 1950 (Box 477, Folder 3199)
    - Staff - International - Miscellany - (H-Pol), 1950 (Box 477, Folder 3200)
    - Staff - International - Miscellany - (Pop-Rob), 1950 (Box 477, Folder 3201)
    - Staff - International - Miscellany - (Rub-St), 1950 (Box 477, Folder 3202)
    - Staff - International - Miscellany - (Sw-Z), 1950 (Box 477, Folder 3203)
    - Staff - International - (O-T), 1950 (Box 478, Folder 3204)
  - United States, 1950; 02.1950/200
    - United States - (A-Az), 1950 (Box 478, Folder 3205)
    - United States - (American A-I), 1950 (Box 478, Folder 3206)
    - United States - (American A-I), 1950 (Box 478, Folder 3207)
    - United States - (American A-I), 1950 (Box 478, Folder 3208)
    - United States - (American A-I), 1950 (Box 478, Folder 3209)
    - United States - (American J-Z), 1950 (Box 479, Folder 3210)
    - United States - (American J-Z), 1950 (Box 479, Folder 3211)
    - United States - (Association A-Z), 1950 (Box 479, Folder 3212)
    - United States - (B), 1950 (Box 479, Folder 3213)
    - United States - (Ca), 1950 (Box 479, Folder 3214)
    - United States - (Carnegie A-Z), 1950 (Box 479, Folder 3215)
    - United States - (Carter and Jones), 1950 (Box 480, Folder 3216)
    - United States - (Cb-Ch), 1950 (Box 480, Folder 3217)
    - United States - (Ci-Col), 1950 (Box 480, Folder 3218)
    - United States - Columbia University, 1950 (Box 480, Folder 3219)
    - United States - (Com-Cz), 1950 (Box 480, Folder 3220)
    - United States - (D), 1950 (Box 480, Folder 3221)
    - United States - (Ea-Ec), 1950 (Box 481, Folder 3222)
    - United States - (Ed-Ez), 1950 (Box 481, Folder 3223)
    - United States - (Fa-Fe), 1950 (Box 481, Folder 3224)
    - United States - (Fi-Fo), 1950 (Box 481, Folder 3225)
    - United States - (Fr-Fz), 1950 (Box 481, Folder 3226)
    - United States - (G), 1950 (Box 482, Folder 3227)
    - United States - Hackett, Lewis W., 1950 (Box 482, Folder 3228)
    - United States - (Ha-Har), 1950 (Box 482, Folder 3229)
    - United States - Harvard University - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 482, Folder 3230)
    - United States - Harvard University - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 482, Folder 3231)
    - United States - Harvard University - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 482, Folder 3232)
    - United States - (Has-Hez), 1950 (Box 483, Folder 3233)
    - United States - (Hf-Hz), 1950 (Box 483, Folder 3234)
    - United States - (I-Ins), 1950 (Box 483, Folder 3235)
    - United States - (Institutes), 1950 (Box 483, Folder 3236)
    - United States - (Int-Iz), 1950 (Box 483, Folder 3237)
    - United States - (J-K), 1950 (Box 483, Folder 3238)
    - United States - (La-Lib), 1950 (Box 484, Folder 3239)
    - United States - (Library of Congress), 1950 (Box 484, Folder 3240)
    - United States - (Lic-Lz), 1950 (Box 484, Folder 3241)
    - United States - (Ma), 1950 (Box 484, Folder 3242)
    - United States - (Mi-Me), 1950 (Box 484, Folder 3243)
    - United States - (Mf-Mz), 1950 (Box 484, Folder 3244)
    - United States - (N-Nas), 1950 (Box 485, Folder 3245)
    - United States - (National A-Z), 1950 (Box 485, Folder 3246)
    - United States - (National A-Z), 1950 (Box 485, Folder 3247)
    - United States - (Nat-Nez), 1950 (Box 485, Folder 3248)
    - United States - (Nf-Oz), 1950 (Box 485, Folder 3249)
    - United States - (Pa), 1950 (Box 485, Folder 3250)
    - United States - (Pe-Pz), 1950 (Box 486, Folder 3251)
    - United States - (Pe-Pz), 1950 (Box 486, Folder 3252)
    - United States - (Q-Re), 1950 (Box 486, Folder 3253)
    - United States - (Rh-Ro), 1950 (Box 486, Folder 3254)
    - United States - (Ru-Rz), 1950 (Box 486, Folder 3255)
    - United States - (Sa-Sc), 1950 (Box 486, Folder 3256)
    - United States - (Se-Sq), 1950 (Box 487, Folder 3257)
    - United States - (Sr-Sy), 1950 (Box 487, Folder 3258)
    - United States - (Sz-Uni), 1950 (Box 487, Folder 3259)
    - United States - Unitarian Service Committee, 1950 (Box 487, Folder 3260)
    - United States - Unitarian Service Committee, 1950 (Box 487, Folder 3261)
    - United States - Unitarian Service Committee, 1950 (Box 487, Folder 3262)
    - United States - (U), 1950 (Box 488, Folder 3263)
    - United States - (United States: A-Z), 1950 (Box 488, Folder 3264)
    - United States - (United States: A-Z), 1950 (Box 488, Folder 3265)
    - United States - (United States: PHS), 1950 (Box 488, Folder 3266)
    - United States - (United States - State Department A-W), 1950 (Box 488, Folder 3267)
    - United States - (United States - State Department A-W), 1950 (Box 488, Folder 3268)
    - United States - (V), 1950 (Box 488, Folder 3269)
    - United States - (Wa), 1950 (Box 489, Folder 3270)
    - United States - (We-Wi), 1950 (Box 489, Folder 3271)
    - United States - (Wo-Wz), 1950 (Box 489, Folder 3272)
    - United States - (X-Z), 1950 (Box 489, Folder 3273)
  - United States - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/200.A
    - United States, 1950 (Box 489, Folder 3274)
  - United States - Nursing, 1950; 02.1950/200.C
    - United States, 1950 (Box 489, Folder 3275)
  - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/200.E
    - United States, 1950 (Box 489, Folder 3275)
  - United States - Public Health Education, 1950; 02.1950/200.L
    - United States, 1950 (Box 489, Folder 3275)
  - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/200.R
    - United States, 1950 (Box 489, Folder 3276)
  - United States - Social Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/200.S
    - United States - (A-P), 1950 (Box 490, Folder 3277)
    - United States - (S-Z), 1950 (Box 490, Folder 3278)
  - Alabama, 1950; 02.1950/201
    - Alabama, 1950 (Box 490, Folder 3279)
  - California, 1950; 02.1950/205
    - California, 1950 (Box 490, Folder 3280)
    - University of California - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 490, Folder 3281)
    - University of California - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 490, Folder 3282)
  - California - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/205.A
    - California, 1950 (Box 490, Folder 3283)
  - California - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/205.R
    - California, 1950 (Box 490, Folder 3283)
  - Panama Canal Zone, 1950; 02.1950/206
    - Canal Zone, 1950 (Box 490, Folder 3284)
  - Colorado, 1950; 02.1950/207
  - Colorado - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/207.A
    - Colorado, 1950 (Box 490, Folder 3284)
  - Colorado - Social Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/207.S
    - Colorado, 1950 (Box 490, Folder 3284)
  - Connecticut, 1950; 02.1950/208
    - Connecticut, 1950 (Box 490, Folder 3285)
  - Florida, 1950; 02.1950/211
    - Florida, 1950 (Box 490, Folder 3285)
  - Georgia, 1950; 02.1950/212
    - Georgia, 1950 (Box 490, Folder 3285)
  - Hawaii, 1950; 02.1950/214
    - Hawaii, 1950 (Box 490, Folder 3285)
  - Illinois, 1950; 02.1950/216
    - Illinois - (A-P), 1950 (Box 491, Folder 3286)
    - Illinois - University of Chicago - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 491, Folder 3287)
    - University of Illinois, 1950 (Box 491, Folder 3288)
  - Illinois - Social Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/216.S
    - University of Illinois, 1950 (Box 491, Folder 3288)
  - Indiana, 1950; 02.1950/217
    - Indiana, 1950 (Box 491, Folder 3289)
  - Kansas, 1950; 02.1950/219
    - Kansas, 1950 (Box 491, Folder 3289)
  - Louisiana, 1950; 02.1950/221
    - Louisiana, 1950 (Box 491, Folder 3289)
  - Louisiana - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 02.1950/221.D
    - Louisiana, 1950 (Box 491, Folder 3289)
  - Maine, 1950; 02.1950/222
    - Maine, 1950 (Box 491, Folder 3289)
  - Maryland, 1950; 02.1950/223
    - Maryland, 1950 (Box 491, Folder 3289)
  - Massachusetts, 1950; 02.1950/224
    - Massachusetts, 1950 (Box 491, Folder 3290)
  - Michigan, 1950; 02.1950/225
    - Michigan, 1950 (Box 491, Folder 3290)
  - Mississippi, 1950; 02.1950/227
    - Mississippi, 1950 (Box 491, Folder 3290)
  - Missouri, 1950; 02.1950/228
    - Missouri, 1950 (Box 491, Folder 3290)
  - New York, 1950; 02.1950/235
    - New York, 1950 (Box 491, Folder 3291)
  - New York - Nursing, 1950; 02.1950/235.C
    - New York, 1950 (Box 491, Folder 3291)
  - New York - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/235.R
    - New York, 1950 (Box 491, Folder 3291)